Guide to the New York State Council on the Arts Electronic Media and Film Program records, [ca. 1960-2011]
New York State Council on the Arts Electronic Media and Film Program records
- Individuals A-Z
  - A-C
    - Dean Curtis Bear Claw, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 136)
      Grant application FY99 for Kevin Red Star: Crow Indian Artist; letter of agreement
    - Cochrane, Chris - PS122 (E 124), 1990 (Box 10, Folder 137)
      Correspondence; grant application FY90 for Slight of Hand
    - Cockburn, Alexander - Creation Production Co., c. 1988 (Box 10, Folder 138)
      Project description for FDR Remembers Pearl Harbor; correspondence
    - Cohen, Adam - Standby Program, Inc. (VD 45), 1996 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Grant application FY97 for Voyage to El Xino; final report FY1996-1997; correspondence
    - Cohen, Jem - NYFA (VA 43), c. 1995, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Grant application (FY95 and undated) for Lost Book Found; correspondence; work in progress report
    - Cohen, Maxi - Video Repertorie (VN 39), c. 1987, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      Grant application (1987-1988, 1989-1990) for Jones Beach and How Much is Really True; correspondence
    - Cohen, Pamela - Now and Then Productions (VD 36), 1986, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      Grant application 1986-1987 for Maria's Story; press release 1991
    - Cokes, Tony - Haleakala (VA 52) (IND), c. 1988, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Grant application 1988-1989 for Love, Labor, Language (The Time and the Memory); letter of agreement 1992
    - Cole, Kermit - Media Network (VD 51)(IND), 1992, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Grant application FY94 for Living Proof; letter of agreement (1992)
    - Collingnon, Bob, c. 1983 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      Letter of agreement for billboard project; CV For Robert Collignon; press release; copies of news clippings
    - Collins, Lisa, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      Letter of agreement
    - Collins, Nicholas - Harvestworks (EL 9) (IND), c. 1985-1992 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      Grant applications (1985-1986, 1988, 1989-1990, FY92) for an audio installation, music composition, Table de Seance and Conductor,
    - Colon, Francisco, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
      Project description for Secret Acts
    - Colon, Willie (JZ 252), c. 1987, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
      Correspondence; sample of the work submitted form; biography of Willie Colon
    - Colquhoun, Michael - Hallwalls, Inc. (JZ 10), c. 1997 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      Final Report Form 1997-1998 for general music support; CV for Michael Colquhoun
    - Connors, Richard, c. 1987 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      Grant application 1987-1988 for Eden is Burning
    - Cook, Cathy C. - Standby Program, Inc.(VE 49), c. 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      Grant application FY98 for Beyond Voluntary Control; Final Report form FY 1997-1998
    - Conrad, Tony - Center for Exploratory and Perceptual Art (VA 44), c. 1985 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      Grant application 1985-1986 Given to the Best
    - Corfield, Loraine - 185 Nassau Street Corp.(VD 46), c. 1985 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for untitled video project
    - Cornyn, Alison, undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
      panel findings
    - Consoli, Marc-Antonio (CV 225), undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
      Project description for Greek Lyrics; sample of the work submitted form
    - Corris, Michael - Franklin Furnace Archive (AG 32), 1987 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      Correspondence, grant application 1986-1987 for Typographic Samples, Pictures and Polemics, Part II
    - Corocoran, Lynn (VD 53), c. 1984, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      Grant application 1988-1989 for Borderline Considerations; checklist 1984-1985; project description (c. 1984) for Niagara River Project
    - Cowen, Robert (F 39E), c. 1984 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      Grant application 1984-1985 for 10 Women 10
    - Cowie, Norman - Alternative Media Information Center (VA 43), c. 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 22)
      Grant application (1991-1992, 1992-1993) for War is a Violent Crime
    - Crane, Ben - Experimental Television Center (VD 51), c. 1996 (Box 11, Folder 23)
      Grant application FY97 for School Prayer: A Community Divided
    - Cream, Melanie, c. 2001 (Box 11, Folder 24)
      Grant application FY01 Phantom Limb
    - Cruz, M. - River Arts Repertory (PW 13), c. 1994 (Box 11, Folder 25)
      Grant application 1994-1995 for Children of War Theater Project
    - Cseri-Briones, Pia - Visual Studies Workshop (VD 55), c. 1996 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      Grant application FY96 for Rosalia and Emilia at the Edge of the River
    - Cruz, Nilo - New York Theater Workshop, Inc. (IND), c. 1998 (Box 11, Folder 27)
      Final Report form FY 1998-1999 for a play about Cuba
    - Curran, Keith - Circle Repertory Company, c. 1990 (Box 11, Folder 28)
      Grant application 1990-1991 for Church of the Sole Survivor
    - Currie, Russell (OP 46), 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 29)
      Correspondence; letter of agreement (1988); sample of work submitted form
    - Cypriano, Tania - Camera News, Inc. (VD 53), c. 1997 (Box 11, Folder 30)
      Grant application (FY97, FY94) for Aids and Candomble and Odo Ya!: Life with AIDS; CV for Tania Cypriano
  - D-F
    - D'Antonio, Emile and Alan Siegel - Camera News, Inc.(V 43D), c. 1984 (Box 11, Folder 31)
      Grant application 1984-1985 for Gravestones and Souls
    - Daum, Menachem - Alternative media Information Center (VD 51), 1998 (Box 11, Folder 32)
      Correspondence, grant application FY98 for Give Us Harmony: The Music and Message of Rabbi Shlomo Carlebach
    - Davidovsky, Mario - Speculum Musicae (CH 27), undated (Box 11, Folder 33)
      Sample of the work submitted form
    - Davis, Anthony - Harvestworks (CV 210), undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
      Grant application for music composition
    - Davis, Collis (VN 60), c. 1987, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 35)
      Grant application 1987-1988 for Elegba's Stratagem; progress report 1989
    - Davis, Peter - Delaware Valley Arts Alliance (VD 48), c. 1985 (Box 11, Folder 36)
      Grant application 1985-1986; proposed film form (undated)
    - Deep Dish (SP 1), c. 1992 (Box 11, Folder 37)
      Grant application 1992-1993 for new series
    - Demarinis, Paul - Audio Art Harvestworks, c. 1987 (Box 11, Folder 38)
      Grant application (1987-1988, undated) for Online Opera, Voice Creatures and Tellus
    - Deihim, S. and Richard Horwitz - Harvestworks (ST 28), c. 1988, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 39)
      Grant application (1988-1989, FY90) for The Weight of a Gaze and The Big Mirror; correspondence
    - DeLeo, Maryann - Downtown Community TV Center (VD 55), undated (Box 11, Folder 40)
      Grant application (undated) for film about foreign adoption
    - DelGaudio, S. and Wineapple - Women Make Movies (VD 59), c. 1996 (Box 11, Folder 41)
      Grant application FY96 Beyond Pigs and Bunnies
    - Denes, Agnes (IA 3), c. 1984 (Box 11, Folder 42)
      Grant application 1984-1985 for Book of Dust
    - Denis, Nelson - Latino Collaborative (VN 150), undated (Box 11, Folder 43)
      Grant application (undated) Lenny's Prayer
    - Deschamps, Francois - Visual Studies Workshop (AP 37), c. 1986 (Box 11, Folder 44)
      Grant application 1986-1987 for The Revenge of the Slapstick Papyrus
    - Devlin, Lucinda and John Orentlicher - Light Work Visual Studies, undated (Box 11, Folder 45)
      Grant application (undated) for piece examining the Contemporary Pleasure Industry; copy of news clippings
    - Diamond, David and the 92nd Street YMCA (V 165), undated (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Dick, Robert - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute (EL 29), c. 1990 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Diekman, Kristine - Harvestworks (VA 67) (IND), c. 1992 (Box 11, Folder 48)
      Grant application 1992-1993 for Male Mating Calls of Manhattan
    - Diesendruck, Tamar - Washington Square Contemporary Music (CH 44), c. 1989 (Box 11, Folder 49)
      Grant application (undated) for Quartet and Etudes
    - Doruff, Sher -Livewalk (EL 30), c. 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 50)
      Correspondence; grant application FY90 for The Escape Artist
    - Dougherty, Cecilia, c. 1998-2000 (Box 11, Folder 51)
      Grant application FY99 for Gone; Final Report form FY 1998-1999; correspondence
    - Doura, Daniel - New York Hispanic-American Dance Company (Ballet Hispanico of New York) (S 105), c. 1986 (Box 11, Folder 52)
      Grant application (undated c. 1986) for Bernarda
    - Dove, Toni - Harvestworks (VI 89), c. 1995, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 53)
      Grant application (FY95, FY01) for Artificial Changelings and Spectropia
    - Downey, Juan - Raindance (VD 56), 1985-1991 (Box 11, Folder 54)
      Grant applications (1985, 1989-1990, FY91) for J.S. Bach, Shifters, and Hard Times and Culture; correspondence
    - Dreher, Stephen and Kevin Cloutier- Cooperative Network Development Association (VD 54), c. 1985 (Box 11, Folder 55)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for In the Blood
    - Drexler, Rosalyn - Theater for the New City, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 56)
      Grant application 1995-1993 for Naked Desire; correspondence
    - Driscoll, Ellen - Snug Harbor Cultural Center (WS011), c. 1998 (Box 11, Folder 57)
      Grant application FY 1998-1999 for Ahab's Wife
    - Driver, Sara, c1984-1987 (Box 11, Folder 58)
      Grant application 1984-1985 for Tale of Suzanne - retitled Sleepwalk (Jim Jarmusch - camera)
    - Drummond, Dean - Newband (ST 15), c. 1992 (Box 11, Folder 59)
      Grant application FY92 for Incredible Time (To Live and Die)
    - DuBovski, Sandi - New York Lesbian and Gay Exper. Fe (Mix) (VD 90), c. 1995 (Box 11, Folder 60)
      Grant application FY95 for Faux Peyes
    - Dukie, Goran - Samaya Foundation (VN 92) (IND), c. 1995 (Box 11, Folder 61)
      Grant application FY95 for Marc (30)
    - Dun, T. and Chuma - School of Hard Knocks (SD 32), undated (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - Duran, Esther - Association of Hispanic Arts (VN 66) (IND), c. 1990, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 63)
      Grant application (1990 and FY94) for Anacleto Morones
    - Dwass, Michael - Millenium (VA 56), 1991 (Box 11, Folder 64)
      Grant application (FY92) for Endless Tango; letter of agreement
    - Ebrahimian, Ghasem, and Coleen Higgins - Alternative Media Information Center (VN 52), c. 1986 (Box 11, Folder 65)
      Grant application 1986-1987 for The Suiters
    - Echeverria, Diego - Cine Information, Inc. (V 48D), 1984 (Box 11, Folder 66)
      Grant application 1984-1985 for Scientists in the Age of Super-Weapons; letter of agreement
    - Egloff, Elizabeth - New York Theater Workshop (19), c. 1992 (Box 11, Folder 67)
      Grant application 1992-1993 for The Civil War
    - Ehn, Erik - The Brooklyn Arts Council (BACA), c. 1990 (Box 11, Folder 68)
      Grant application 1990-1991 for The Saint Plays
    - Ehrlich, Marty - Musicians of Brooklyn Initiative (J 86), c.1986 (Box 11, Folder 69)
      Sample of work submitted form; copies of news clippings; letter of agreement
    - Eiferman, Lee - NYFA (VN 63), c. 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 70)
      Grant application (1985-1986, 1986-1987) for Ena's Adventures
    - Eison, Carvin and Garth Fagan - Grth Fagaan's Bucket Dance Theater (VD 164), 1987 (Box 11, Folder 71)
      Grant application 1987-1988 for a documentary film on Garth Fagan's Bucket tour of Africa; letter of agreement
    - Ekhart, Rinde (Mabou Miners) (ST 261), undated (Box 11, Folder 72)
      Grant application (undated) for The Mormon Project
    - Elson, Steve - Dance Theater Workshop (JZ 33), c. 1990 (Box 11, Folder 73)
      Grant application FY90 for Bands on the Run
    - Engel, Herman - The Film Fund (VD 59), c. 1985 (Box 11, Folder 74)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for a documentary on Nicaragua
    - Erikson, Gordon - NYFA (VN 64), 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 75)
      Grant application 1989-1990 for Ain't Nobody; letter of agreement
    - Evans, Amee and Carol Saft, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 76)
      Grant application 1989-1990 for Shared Ground; letter of agreement
    - Evans, Rodney, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 77)
      Committee comments; letter of agreement
    - Even, Tierza - Harvestworks, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 78)
    - Even, Tierza - Harvestworks, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 79)
      Grant application FY97 for Color Blind; letter of agreement
    - Ewazen, Eric - St. Luke's Chamber Ensemble (CH 21), c. 1997 (Box 11, Folder 80)
      Grant application FY1997-1998 for Mandala
    - Exit 3 Productions, c. 1995, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 81)
      Grant application FY95 for Jazzplay; letter of agreement (1998)
    - Eyre, Chris - American Indian Artists (Amerinda), Inc., 1999 (Box 11, Folder 82)
      Grant application FY 1999-2000 for $ilverheels; letter of agreement
    - Felder, David (OR 70), c. 1990 (Box 11, Folder 83)
      Grant application FY90 for Between
    - Fennelly, Brian - Foundation for Baroque Music, c. 1986 (Box 11, Folder 84)
      Sample of work submitted form; biography of Brian Fennelly; letter of agreement
    - Field, Rachel (VD 72), c. 1988 (Box 11, Folder 85)
      Grant application 1988-1989 for Marri-Chihueu: Ten Times, We Will Overcome
    - Feingold, Ken - Electronic Arts Intermix (VI 59), unadted and c.1991 (Box 11, Folder 86)
      Grant application (undated, 1991-1992) for The Double and for a untitled interactive single-channel computer controlled videodisk, with objects
    - Filippo, Mary (VE 73), c. 1988, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 87)
      Grant applications 1988-1989, FY91 for Feel the Fear
    - Fine, Vivian - Capitol Chamber Artists (CH 60), c. 1986, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 88)
      Grant application (undated) for a commissioned piece of music; letter of agreement (1986, 1988)
    - Finley, Jeanne C., 2000 (Box 11, Folder 89)
      Grant application FY01 for Loss Prevention; committee comments
    - Fisher, Holly - Women Make Movies, Inc., c. 1989-1999 (Box 11, Folder 90)
      Grant applications (1989-1990, 1990, FY97, FY 1998-1999) for Unorganized Territory, Bullets for Breakfast, Burma Land/Scapes and an unnamed project
    - Fisher, Linda - Audio Art Rio Grande Union, Inc. (A 30), 1984 (Box 11, Folder 91)
      Grant application 1984-1985 for Text Work for Voice and Micro Computer
    - Fitch, Claudia, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 92)
      Grant application FY89 for a sculpture installation in the Garden at Mohawk Valley Psychiatric Center; letter of agreement
    - Flanary, Lisette Marie, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 93)
      Committee comments
    - Flanders, Laura and Andrea Kirsch - Now and Then Production (VD 63), c. 1985 (Box 11, Folder 94)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for The Longest Strike
    - Flanders, Laura and Mary Jane Sullivan - Out There Productions (VD 68), c. 1985 (Box 11, Folder 95)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for What is the difference Between a Country and a House?
    - Foreman, Richard and Ed Bowes - Haleakala (VN 68), c. 1989 (Box 11, Folder 96)
      Two grant applications 1989-1990 for Lava and Total Rain
    - Fornes, Maria Irene - International Arts Relations (Di 20), 1989, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 97)
      Grant application (1989-1990, 1996-1997) for Silent Twins and Terra Incognita
    - Fast Forward - Experimental Intermedia Foundation, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 98)
      Grant application FY92; sample of work submitted form; letter of agreement
    - Fox, Curtis, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 99)
      panel comments; letter of agreement
    - Fraher, Diane and Clinton Elliot, c. 1998 (Box 11, Folder 100)
      Grant application FY98 for The Reawakening
    - Franceschi, Edgar -Intar (X 56), c. 1986 (Box 11, Folder 101)
      Grant application 1986-1987 for Memories to Burn (or Veni, Creator Spiritus)
    - Francovich, Allan - Foundation for Open Company, Inc. (FD 63), c. 1986 (Box 11, Folder 102)
      Grant application for 1986-1987 for The Houses are Full of Smoke
    - Frank - NYFA (A 40), 1984 (Box 11, Folder 103)
      Grant application 1984-1985 for The Notebooks of Joseph Molka
    - Freedman, Joel - NYFA (VD 79), c. 1987 (Box 11, Folder 104)
      Grant application 1987-1988 for Broken Treaty - Return to Battle Mountain
    - Freer, Lynn and Dale Goodson - Open Channells/ Dixson Place - (PE 58), undated (Box 11, Folder 105)
      Grant application (undated) for We die, You Die based on Thornton Wilder's Our Town
    - Frew, Suzanne - Visual Studies Workshop, c. 1985 (Box 11, Folder 106)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for Beneath the Safety Net
    - Friedman, Sonya - Rensselaer County Council Arts (VD 78), c. 1989 (Box 11, Folder 107)
      Grant application 1989-1990 for The Song of the Lark
    - Friedrich, Su - Jezebel Productions (VE 76), c. 1986-1999 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      Grant application (1986-1987, 1989-1990, FY94) for Breaking the Habit, Happy New Year, and Even Then; letter of agreement (1999)
    - Friedman, Peter - Media Network (VD 81), c. 1992 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      Grant application (1992-1993, FY93) for Silverlake Life
    - Friedman, Steve - Asian Arts Center (WS013) (IND), c. 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 110)
      Grant application 1998-1999, for Translation/ Planting/ Formation; correspondence
    - Frilot, Shari - New York Lesbian and Gay Experience Film Festival (VN 70), c. 1998 (Box 11, Folder 111)
      Grant application FY98 for Strange and Charmed
    - Frost, Everett - Harvestworks (RA 30), undated c. 1990 (Box 11, Folder 112)
      Grant application (undated) for Sound Play
    - Fusco, Juliana (Coco) - Camera News (RA 64), c. 1991 (Box 11, Folder 113)
      Grant application 1991-1992 for Norte: Sur II - Son de Nueva York
  - G-I
    - Gabay, Yuval - Experimental Intermedia Foundation (SD 23), c. 1992 (Box 11, Folder 114)
      Grant application FY92 for ceases, still i see
    - Galembo, Phyllis - Catskill Center for Photography (Ph 53), 1982, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 115)
      Grant application 1987-1988 for Ritual Art and Sacred Spaces; letter of agreement (1982, 1987)
    - Gam, Kaja - Hallwalls (V 59) (PE 45), c. 1986, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 116)
      Grant application (1986-1987, FY89) for Translocation 9:16 and Conversations with an Entrance; correspondence; handwritten notes
    - Garces, Michael John - American Place (PW 45), c. 1994 (Box 11, Folder 117)
      Grant application 1994-1995 for Las Mantanas, Mi Cara, Todo Un Laberinto
    - Garcia, Alraro - Friends of Puerto Rico, Inc (Museum of Contemporary Hispanic Art (MoCHA)(PA 55), c. 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 118)
      Grant application 1987-1988 for Alvaro Garcia: Recent Paintings; letter of agreement
    - Garcia, William - NYFA (VD 90), c. 1990 (Box 11, Folder 119)
      Grant application 1990 for A Day at a Time
    - Garland, David - WNYC Foundation (ST 223), 1988 (Box 11, Folder 120)
    - Garrin, Paul - NYFA (VD 73), c. 1989 (Box 11, Folder 121)
      Grant application 1989-1990 for By Any Means Necessary
    - Gatewood, Charles, undated (Box 11, Folder 122)
      Proposal for Wall Street
    - Gazit, C. and Steward - Hallwalls (VD 74), c. 1989 (Box 11, Folder 123)
      Grant application 1989-1990 for Honorable Nations
    - Gehr, Ernie - Collective for Living Cinema (F 63E), c. 1984 (Box 11, Folder 124)
      Grant application 1984-1985 for unnamed project
    - Geiser, Janie - Arts at St. Ann's (IND), c. 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 125)
      Grant application 1998-1999 for Ether Telegrams; letter of agreement
    - Geiser, Janie - Dance Theater Workshop (VA 81), c. 1994-1999 (Box 11, Folder 126)
      Grant application (1994-1995, FY96, 1998-1999) for Betty's Suffer's Theory of Relativity, Magnetic Sleep and Ether Telegrams
    - Gerber, Tony - Mabou Mines (VN 82), c. 1996 (Box 11, Folder 127)
      Grant application FY96 for Kitzel Park; press and biographical materials
    - Geller, Matthew - NYFA (VN 84), c. 1983-1987 (Box 11, Folder 128)
      Grant application (1984-1985, 1986-1987) for Everglades and Upwardly Mobile Home (UMH); supporting materials; letters of agreement NYFA 1983 and 1986; correspondence
    - Georges, Basilio - Spanish Dance Arts Co. (SD 66), c. 1988 (Box 11, Folder 129)
      Grant application 1988-1989 for a work based on For Whom the Bell Tolls; supporting materials
    - Giannini, A. Christina - Foundation for Independent Artists, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 130)
      Grant application 1990-1991 for Praise House; supporting materials; letter of agreement
    - Giard, Robert, (PH 57), 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 131)
      Grant application 1987-1988 for Particular Voices: Portraits of Gay and Lesbian Writers; letter of agreement; supporting materials; correspondence
    - Gibbons, Joseph - Segue Foundation (VN 83), c. 1996 (Box 11, Folder 132)
      Grant application FY96 for Confessions of a Sociopath
    - Gibson, Jon, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 133)
    - Gibson, John - Antientropy, Inc. (C 10), 1986 (Box 11, Folder 134)
    - Gibson, Linda - Women Make Movies, 1984, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 135)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for Flag; letter of agreement (1984)
    - Gibson, Melissa James, undated (Box 11, Folder 136)
      panel recommendations
    - Gigliotti, Davidson - Experimental Intermedia Foundation (C 9), 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 137)
      Grant application (undated c. 1984) for Storms at Sea
    - Giraud, Tuye - Dance Theater Workshop (ST 37), undated (Box 11, Folder 138)
    - Gitlin, Michale - Millernium (VN 84), c. 1995 (Box 11, Folder 139)
      Grant application FY96 for the The Idea of Teeth; letter of agreement
    - Glass, Jessica - Deep Dish TV, Inc (VD 82), undated (Box 11, Folder 140)
      Grant application (undated) for a series of television programs
    - Godmilow, Jill (VD 85), c. 1988 (Box 11, Folder 141)
      Grant application 1988-1989 for Lear Tapes
    - Gold, Tami - Film Fund (VS 87), c. 1986 (Box 11, Folder 142)
      Grant application 1986-1987 for The Forgotten Ones
    - Goldberg, Neil - Painting Space 122, Inc (IN 86), c. 1997, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 143)
      Grant application (FY97, FY01) for Hallelujah Anyway and Random Walk; panel comments
    - Goldenthal, Elliot (OR 17), undated (Box 11, Folder 144)
      Sample of work submitted form for music composition; biography of Elliot Goldenthal; letter of agreement
    - Goldfarb, Sidney - Talking Band, c. 1989 (Box 11, Folder 145)
      Grant application 1989-1990 for This is Our Music; letter of agreement
    - Goldson, Annie and Chris Bratton - Alternative Media Information Center (VD 78), c. 1986, 1989-1991 (Box 11, Folder 146)
      Grant application (1989-1990, FY91) for CounterTerror: The United States Segment and Counterterror: a)The North of Ireland b) Framing the Panthers in Black and White; letter of agreement (1986)
    - Goldstein, Amy - NYFA (VN 94), c. 1987 (Box 11, Folder 147)
      Grant application 1987-1988 for Because the Dawn
    - Golub, Leon - Artist's Production Press (IA 6), 1984 (Box 11, Folder 148)
      Grant application 1984-1985 for Control and Coercion; letter of agreement
    - Gonzalez, Marina - Film News Now (VN 87), c. 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 149)
      Grant application FY90-91 for Songs My Father Taught Me; final report form
    - Gordon, Ain, undated (Box 11, Folder 150)
      Background information on Ain Gordon
    - Gordon, Bette - Collective for Living Cinema (VN 98), c. 1987, 96 (Box 11, Folder 151)
      Grant application (1987-1988, FY96) for unnamed film project and The History of Luminous Motion
    - Gordon, David - Pick-up Performance Co. (VA 99), c. 1987 (Box 11, Folder 152)
      Grant application 1987-1988 for My Folks
    - Gordon, Frank = Association for the Advancement of Creative Musicians (JZ 69), c. 1988 (Box 11, Folder 153)
      Grant application (undated) for music composition; letter of agreement
    - Gordon, Michael - Bang on a Can (SF 43), c. 1990 (Box 11, Folder 154)
      Grant application FY90 for Van Gogh Video; letter of agreement
    - Gordon, Peter - NYFA (SF 44), undated (Box 11, Folder 155)
      Grant application (undated) for Marco Polo in America